<!-- Plugin Configuration File. Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <!-- Unique identifier of the plugin. It should be FQN. It cannot be changed between the plugin versions. -->
    <id>com.luweijie.dev.gear.InteractiveSqlGenerator</id>

    <!-- Public plugin name should be written in Title Case.
         Guidelines: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/marketplace/plugin-overview-page.html#plugin-name -->
    <name>InteractiveSqlGenerator</name>
    ````````
    <!-- A displayed Vendor name or Organization ID displayed on the Plugins Page. -->
    <vendor email="1397100450@qq.com">DevGear</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
<h1>Interactive SQL Generator</h1>

<p>Simplify your database operations with the Interactive SQL Generator plugin for IntelliJ IDEA. This powerful tool allows you to effortlessly generate SQL  and MyBatis/MyBatis-Plus code for your Java projects.</p>

<h2>Key Features:</h2>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Interactive UI</strong>: Easily select fields, conditions, and mappings through a user-friendly interface.</li>
    <li><strong>Multiple SQL Types</strong>: Generate SELECT, INSERT, UPDATE, and DELETE  with just a few clicks.</li>
    <li><strong>ORM Support</strong>: Choose between MyBatis and MyBatis-Plus for your preferred Object-Relational Mapping.</li>
    <li><strong>Custom Conditions</strong>: Set specific conditions for each field in your WHERE clauses.</li>
    <li><strong>Database Entity Mapping</strong>: Map your Java classes to database entities for accurate SQL generation.</li>
    <li><strong>Clipboard Integration</strong>: Copy generated SQL or Java code directly to your clipboard for quick use.</li>
</ul>

<p>Whether you're working on a new project or maintaining legacy code, the Interactive SQL Generator streamlines your database interaction development process, saving you time and reducing errors.</p>

<h2>Usage Instructions:</h2>

<ol>
    <li><strong>Activation</strong>: Right-click in your Java file or use the Tools menu to activate the Interactive SQL Generator.</li>
    <li><strong>Class Selection</strong>: Choose your Java class and corresponding database entity class when prompted.</li>
    <li><strong>SQL Type and ORM</strong>: Select the type of SQL operation (SELECT, INSERT, UPDATE, DELETE) and your preferred ORM (MyBatis or MyBatis-Plus).</li>
    <li><strong>Field Selection</strong>: In the interactive table, choose which fields to include in your query.</li>
    <li><strong>Condition Setting</strong>: For each selected field, specify the condition (e.g., =, >, LIKE) and the connection type (AND/OR).</li>
    <li><strong>Generate</strong>: Click "OK" to generate your SQL or Java code.</li>
    <li><strong>Review and Copy</strong>: Review the generated code in the results window. Use the "Copy to Clipboard" button to easily paste it into your project.</li>
    <li><strong>Iterate</strong>: If needed, use the "Back" button to adjust your selections and regenerate the code.</li>
</ol>

<p>Get started today and experience the power of effortless SQL generation!</p>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>




    <!-- Extension points defined by the plugin.
         Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-extension-points.html -->
    <!-- 注册项目活动 -->
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <postStartupActivity implementation="com.dev.gear.PluginInitializer"/>
    </extensions>
    <actions>
        <action id="Interactive Sql Generator" class="com.dev.gear.InteractiveSqlGeneratorAction"
                text="Interactive Sql Generator" description="Interactive Sql Generator">
            <add-to-group group-id="GenerateGroup" anchor="last"/>

            <!-- 这里配置快捷键 -->
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="ctrl shift L"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>